{
  "chapters": [
    {
      "name": "Chapter 1",
      "description": "Alerts",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "questionText": "What is the keyword that displays a message box?",
          "questionType": 1,
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "alert"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "questionText": "Type the character that ends every statement.",
          "questionType": 1,
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": ";"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "questionText": "Type the 2 characters that are missing in this statement.",
          "subText": "alert\"You're learning JavaScript!\";",
          "questionType": 1,
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "()"
        },{
          "id": 3,
          "questionText": "Fill in the blank.",
          "questionType": 2,
          "incompleteStatement": "A __ ends in a semicolon.",
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "statement"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "questionText": "Write an alert that displays \"Thanks for everything!\"",
          "questionType": 1,
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "alert(\"Thanks for everything!\");"
        },{
          "id": 6,
          "questionText": "Write an alert that displays \"Boo!\".",
          "questionType": 1,
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "alert(\"Boo!\");"
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "questionText": "The code displays a box with a message in it. Fill in the blank.",
          "questionType": 2,
          "incompleteStatement": " __ (\"You won!\");",
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "alert"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "questionText": "The code displays a box with a message in it. Fill in the blank.",
          "questionType": 2,
          "incompleteStatement": "alert(\"You won!__ ",
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "\");"
        },{
          "id": 9,
          "questionText": "Code an alert that displays the message \"Hi\"",
          "questionType": 1,
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "alert(\"Hi\");"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "questionText": "What are the 5 punctuation characters of an alert statement, in order?",
          "questionType": 1,
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "(\"\");"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter 2",
      "description": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "questionText": "Fill in the blank.",
          "questionType": 2,
          "incompleteStatement": "A __ ends with a semicolon.",
          "answers": [],
          "correctAnswer": "statement"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "questionText": "question2",
          "questionType": 0,
          "answers": [
            "answer1",
            "answer2",
            "answer3",
            "answer4"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "questionText": "question3",
          "questionType": 0,
          "answers": [
            "answer1",
            "answer2",
            "answer3",
            "answer4"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter 3",
      "description": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter 4",
      "description": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter 5",
      "description": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter 6",
      "description": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit",
      "questions": []
    }
  ]
}